Hello everyone welcome to my
youtube1. Stocks which are fundamentally very
strong and we are
seeing them at a good discount price
so that they
can give us a good return in the future. Today
in the video we are going to talk
about ICICI Prudential stock which
we are seeing at a good discount price.
So can some of them be
targets in the future? Can some of them
become its important support and resistance? We will
know in this video. So
before starting the video, if you are visiting our channel for the
first time, then like the video and
subscribe to the channel because
I keep finding such stocks for you daily.
So let's start by talking about the
current price of ICICI Prudential stock. Currently, the stock is
seen trending around ₹4.
If the stock makes a lower circuit from its current price,
then our first important support will be
₹5000000 and important
resistance can be formed around ₹17.
If the stock  If we
break out of the first resistance, then our
second most important resistance can be
formed around 7006. This stock
is fundamentally very strong, so you
can add this stock to your watch list
and if you are related to the share market, then you
can also subscribe to our channel and yes, if you have any question related to this stock,
then you
can also comment to us in the comment box.